



# **Mugia Miftahul Choir**

Date of birth: 18/06/2001 | **Nationality:** Indonesian | **Gender:** Male |

(+62) 83816355113 | mugia.miftahul@gmail.com |

https://mugia.herokuapp.com/

https://www.artstation.com/mugiamiftahulchoir8

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mugia-choir-3b593a1b4/

https://www.instagram.com/mugiadesign/

Whatsapp Messenger: +62 83816355113

Cicadas, Sagalaherang, Subang, Jawa Barat, Indonesia, 41282, Subang, Indonesia

#### About me:

I'm a designer based in Subang, Indonesia that focuses on 3D Graphics. My earliest memory of a design-related experience was when I first opened Adobe Photoshop in early Elementary School. Since then I've gained a lot of experience working on a different scale of projects, from individual projects to corporate class projects. Yet I still have great determination in learning new stuff.

I also have experience of working with people from different countries and cultures, so I can communicate well with others and capable of working alone or inside a team.

I'm majoring in information systems at university, so I have experience in software development, especially front-end development, because it mixes my love for design, and my education as a developer.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

07/2020 - 02/2021 - Subang, Indonesia

WEB DEVELOPER - MTS AL-HIDAYAH SAGALAHERANG

I held all of the jobs in the web development process by myself, including: doing a brief with the client, sketching, wireframing, prototyping, creating high fidelity UI design, designing and implementing a database, front-end, and back-end job

05/2020 - 06/2021 - Subang, Indonesia

**WEB DEVELOPER - SMAN 1 JALANCAGAK SCOUT ORGANIZATION** 

My responsibilities were designing the UI of the website, developing the website according to the design, designing and implementing a database, giving the required training for the users, and maintaining the website after it was online

03/11/2019 - 04/11/2019 - Subang, Indonesia

**GRAPHIC DESIGNER - MAMAH COET RESTAURANT** 

I was only tasked to design a banner for their new opening restaurant, so i started by collecting the assets, choosing the art direction, fonts style, and colors because they didn't have an established brand style to follow yet

30/11/2020 - Subang, Indonesia

**GRAPHIC DESIGNER - MAMAH COET RESTAURANT** 

They came to me to create a simpler version of their logo for some urgent business, so I only have a day to finish the job. What I did was taking a few hours of brainstorming to simplify their logo, aligning my idea with the client, creating a prototype and handing it to them, then doing some revisions

04/09/2021 - 11/02/2022 - Liverpool, United Kingdom

**3D ARTIST - RFIDIOM LTD** 

I was a part of the Marketing Team at RFIDiom Ltd; my main activities were creating graphics content for social media, or blog. But I also contributed to Branding a few of the company's products. And designing UI/UX of a product website.

My special responsibilities were to create 3D assets and create 3D animations; usually, they were used to demo or advertise products.

On occasions I was also responsible for quality assurance on some websites, looking for errors, bugs, etc.

#### EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/07/2021 - 04/07/2021

DIGITAL MARKETING AND GRAPHIC DESIGN TRAINING - PT Inovasi Telematika Nusantara

VirtualTraining.id

31/12/2020 - 16/02/2021

WEB & MOBILLE DESIGN TRAINING - Zero to Mastery

zerotomastery.io

04/11/2020 - 28/12/2020

**REACT.JS TRAINING -** Zero to Mastery

zerotomastery.io

05/03/2021 - 05/04/2021

**REACT NATIVE TRAINING - Zero to Mastery** 

zerotomastery.io

11/06/2020 - 30/06/2020

FUNDAMENTAL FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPMENT TRAINING - Dicoding

dicoding.com

18/06/2021 - 09/09/2021

3D MODELING TRAINING - GameDev.tv

gamedev.tv

15/09/2021 - 28/09/2021

3D CHARACTER CREATOR FOR VIDEO GAMES TRAINING - GameDev.tv

gamedev.tv

## LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): INDONESIAN

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	C1	B2	B2	B2	B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

## DIGITAL SKILLS

Design

Adobe Photoshop | Corel Draw | React - React Native | Adobe Illustrator | Figma

**Programming** 

React ecosystem: ReactJS, React Router, Redux, Typescript | HTML5/CSS3, SASS, JavaScript (including recent versions)

3D

Blender, 3D modeling | 3D animation